(571) 523-3345 McLean, Virginia ytyeung@gwu.edu

# Yat To Yeung, Bosco

# **Ouantitative Social Scientist/ PhD Candidate**

Website: ytyeung.com linkedin.com/in/yeung317

Dedicated and experienced researcher in Asian American identity politics and regulatory politics in Greater China. Keen to leverage quantitative and survey research skills in real-life settings and provide evidence-based solutions to drive positive change.

#### **SKILLS**

Tools and Languages
Quantitative Research

R, Stata, SQL, ŁTFX, Tableau, Qualtrics

Causal Inference, Hierarchical Modeling, Surveys and Experiments, Data Visualization

English, Cantonese, Mandarin

#### **WORKING EXPERIENCE**

PhD CANDIDATE

Communication

AUG 2019 — Present

Washington, DC

George Washington University

- Designed a field experiment and analyzed large survey data with 10000+ respondents to study elite and public decision making.
- Analyzed 6000+ public consultation documents in China, Hong Kong, and Taiwan to examine differences in approaches to civic engagement and regulation.
- Collaborated with 10+ researchers across multiple disciplines on projects that examines Chinese government responsiveness and online hate and anti-vaxx communities in the US.
- Lectured undergraduate students in R tutorial sections and led discussions in American politics class.
- Mentored 20+ undergraduate students on semester-long R research projects.

JUNIOR RESEARCHER

JUN 2018 — AUG 2018

Brussels, Belgium

European Institute for Asian Studies

- Utilized existing data set to co-author a quantitative report on Taiwanese foreign investment in the European Union, commissioned by the Taiwanese Representative Office in Belgium and the EU to promote Taiwan-EU trade.
- Provided operational support to event organization (workshops and briefing seminars).
- · Participated in conferences and seminars organized by think tanks (Bruegel), the European Parliament, and embassies.

## **ADMINISTRATIVE OFFICER (INTERN)**

JUN 2017 — AUG 2017

Home Affairs Department of Hong Kong SAR Government

Hong Kong SAR

- Conducted a qualitative comparative study on homeless policy in Canada, Denmark, Hong Kong, Singapore, U.K., and U.S.
- Refined the Facebook page of the Sham Shui Po Youth Corps by providing recommendations to the District Officer.
- · Participated in the District Council meetings and the public administration of the HKSAR.

SUMMERINTERN

JUN 2016 — AUG 2016 Hong Kong SAR

- The European Chamber of Commerce in Hong Kong
   Conducted research on financial technology policies and automotive industry, particularly in Hong Kong and the European
- Union, for the Business Councils' position papers

  Assembled a report on electric vehicles in Hong Kong for the bilateral negotiation between the EU and HK govt (report presented)
- to the Financial Secretary of Hong Kong and led to the reconsideration of EV subsidies).

   Partnered with and interviewed major automotive manufacturers, fintech, and law firms as part of the research.

#### **EDUCATION**

Doctor of Philosophy in Political Science, George Washington University	May 2024 (expected)
Master of Arts in Political Science, George Washington University	2022
Summer Program in Quantitative Methods of Social Research, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor	2021
Bachelor of Arts in Philosophy, Politics and Economics, University of Michigan, Ann Arbor	2018

# **GRANTS AND FELLOWSHIPS**

ICPSR Summer Program Grant, George Washington University	2021
George Washington University Graduate Student Fellowship	2019-2022
George Washington University Summer Research Fellowship	2019

### **PRESENTATIONS**

111-11111111111111111111111111111111111	
American Political Science Association Annual Meeting	2022 (scheduled)
Asian Politics Online Seminar Series	2021
Northeastern Political Science Association Annual Meeting	2021
Midwest Political Science Association Annual Meeting	2021, 2022
Western Political Science Association Annual Meeting	2021